Hello Invest Bangali channel
welcome to us today our important
topic is
health
insurance. Bharatvarsh has 140 crore
Manushya Raksha Bandhan and NITI Aayog believes that
30 per cent of the people are
not covered by any health insurance scheme. The remaining 70 per cent of the people are covered by health insurance. However, the remaining 70 per cent of the people are covered by
various government
schemes like Ayushman Bharat Swasthya Sathi etc.
but still there are
30 per cent of the people but health insurance is not covered by any health insurance scheme. The first
data is the second data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The second data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The second data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The third data is the
government scheme which has various limitations. The third data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The fourth data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The fourth data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The fourth data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The fourth data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The fourth data is the
government scheme which has various limitations. The fourth data is the government scheme which has various limitations. The fourth data is the government scheme which has various limitations.
Proper health
insurance is not available when the economy is not strong
but proper health insurance is
very important because health insurance is not available due to the fact that in
India the
population is increasing day by day and the number of people living in it is very high. In some
areas the number of people living in it is very high. The economic situation is such that the number of people living in it is increasing. The
main reason behind this is that the medical
expenses are
very low. If you want to know about health insurance then you can take health insurance and get health coverage at one time. If you have any health problem then you can take health insurance at one time and if ...  Apnakar
emergency samay kaje lage eva aad desh lekin GDP mere % khera hoy
health care jan ie maan sabhyata kar tay bujhte pan jeta gota prithvi madhe antyama kum khera tai janya but
apna health insurance thaka khub important
aaj ke hum health insurance ki
swasthya bama anek guli dik na kritika karo
pratham apni kino kinan eva kto amount kinan seta na
hum kritika dekhna health insurance kto saas kinan
seta but depend kar main to manner upar jamun dhar
apni grame tha sethra
apna medical kharf kam abar ta matha krache
grame but critical care nek
samay thake na nek samay na mane infact thake
na se kshetra apnake kono durag dhi hole
apna grame tha city aste ta sabsaat kuchh mathay rekhey
health insurance pratham jhe factor ta mathay rakhne seta hoche apna yas vyas khub important factor jadar vyas ekt  If you take more
than 40 50 years plus then health
insurance amount is more than 40 lakhs but if you
start your employment then this is
less than 40 lakhs but if you take more than 40 lakhs then this health insurance
amount is more than 40 lakhs but if you take more than 40 lakhs then this
health
insurance amount is more than 40 lakhs but it is a very important factor and the second important factor is that you can take more than
40 lakhs then you can take more than 40 lakhs
then this ...  If you are a fat
current jet setter and finally 50 years old then is it
appropriate to get health insurance cover for yourself i.e. if you have a family income of
10 lakh rupees but if you have a family income of
20 lakh rupees
but if you have a family income of minimum 10
lakh rupees then is it
appropriate to get health insurance cover for yourself. If you have a family
income of 3 lakh rupees then should you get
insurance cover for 5 lakh rupees and if you have a
minimum current age of 5 lakh rupees then is it
appropriate to get
health insurance cover for yourself. And if you are looking for health
insurance then do not get health insurance cover for yourself. If you have many options then do not get
health insurance cover for yourself. If you are facing any problem then do not get health insurance cover for yourself.  Health Insurance
Company Limited (HIBITCO) is a leading health insurance company in India that offers various health insurance plans and offers comprehensive health insurance plans. It is
one of the most popular health insurance plans in India and offers comprehensive health insurance plans. It also offers comprehensive health
insurance plans and offers comprehensive health insurance plans. It also offers comprehensive health insurance plans and offers comprehensive health insurance plans.
HDFC
Bank Ltd has launched HDFC Bank Ltd in 2019.
It is a comprehensive policy offering covering various
insurance plans, including various online insurance plans, HDFC Bank Ltd ...
nyanya kon pape jad phone number diye apni
policy kitte chan apni policy kinan ba dekhna ba
na kinan apna ke variyat spam calls aate thake
variyat sales calls aate thake jeta khub
vishta kar dito thake but kon amount e dharan
spam calls apni papan na ta but apna privacy evam
apnakar kaaj jan khub suvidha ho
na hole kaaj naash hoto sales calls n ase sab bada kar rito
platform ekti khub reliance yogy ro dar ekti sunseo
tech startup rae khane roh ceo nikhil kamath jukto tara but apni apni saathe jukto rahe eva
203 lin
bharatvarsh top 20 startup gullo madhe ekti competition kar chalo sekhane dito third position hoye sut apna but khana the
health
policy compare dekhne paab ab humara kota type health policy hote pare dekhne pratham zeta health policy hoy se ho individual insurance policy apni naam sune bujhte pan  If
you have a policy in the name of Ekhane Ek Vyakti Name, that is, you can take a policy in your own
name, your father's name, your child's name, your
wife's name, your family member's name, etc. If you have an individual
policy, you can take a policy in the name of Ekhane Vyakti Name, but if you have a policy in the name of Ekhane Vyakti Name, you can take a
policy in the name of Ekhane Vyakti Name, which will give you a benefit of Rs. 10 lakhs. If you have a family member's name, you can take a single ...
Individually ki
holo dojan astha hoye galo se kshetra dojan kshetra
but ala ala 10 lakh coverage paab
but family planning apna jade dojan astha
ani total 10 lakh coverage me ki apna ke khesh kreti kshetra
but in general dekhna jaa jeetu ekhi parib ekhi bare dujan asta har sambhavna anek kare butan aani ekhi tak coverage chaar paach jan insurance
ek sath kam ta karte pati health coverage
critical illness coverage like cancer kidney
heart attack stroke organ transplant mto
critical coverage gu paab jeetu asu by saap i.e.
critical illness coverage kshetra
insurance by saap besh kuchhu rog listed kar thake
listed kon rog ho apni coverage pe ja
senior citizen health insurance ki bute
naam sune jata jana aa health insurance kara hoye ra
aage senior citizen jana kon health
insurance lo na jeta kshetra an kara ho aur
finaly ek bahub important se maternity
health insurance dekhu ta  Health
Insurance is a family
insurance policy that covers various health
insurance plans like premium,
room rent, pre
and post hospitalization facility, day
care treatment, etc. etc.
Sub limit dekhna sub limit vahan asle ki
t asle mota coverage under tha
various disease treatment ie dharan ani 10
lakh ta coverage karna but ani bhabale sab rogh jan ani
10 lakh na but se nay jamun dhar chokher chhani bahu
insurance policy chokher chhani ja ek
specified amount bad thake ani dharan 10 lakh ta
insuran karna but that insurance company
terms anujai sub limit bole ek kalam thak evam sekhane dekhna jane
chokher chhani ja hoto 500
600 kiba ek lakh eram kuchhu ala bad karna hum chokh chhani
ek example swaroop bola but kumbh bahu rogh rahe
je rogh jany list de hoye e rogh jany
etho khar deya ho er the beshi
khar deya ho na i.e. apnakar insurance kto taka seta shu matra important na joto ta samas insurance ra tar sathe besh kuchhu rogh je rogh jan hi
company sub limit katto  If you are a doctor then you should definitely
go there once and tell me the second
important story of a room which is a very important
topic and should be repeatedly said in the video. If you want to know more about it then please tell me some important things about
insurance sales. If you want to know more about it then please tell me some important things about insurance sales. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance. If you want to know more about insurance then please tell me some important things about insurance.  If
you have a policy of
Rs. 500 then you will have to pay Rs. 000 as initial medical expenses. If you have a
policy of your choice then you will pay Rs.
000 as maximum room rent.
If you need it then you will pay Rs.
000 for every four to five days.
Rest of the claim will be settled. The
company has very good terms and conditions. If
you have a maximum room rent of Rs. 10000 for five days i.e. Rs. 500, then the company will charge Rs. 0000 as room
rent in the policy. If
you have Rs. 10000 for five
days i.e. Rs. 500, then the company will charge Rs. 0000 as room rent. If
your total bill is Rs. 3 lakh then the company will charge Rs. 0000 as room rent. If the
total bill is Rs. 3 lakh then the company will charge Rs. 0000 as room rent.
Rest of the expenses will be paid only at Rs. 60 or Rs. 40, that is
you will have to pay Rs. 3 lakh 60 per month
only.  Ehi karne ki apni apnakar maximum
je room rent policy terms and conditions wise pava katha lo thake beshi renter roome thake chhan sehi janya ta e room rent jo shatra bali seta kant lo dekhne nen evam rakhiya anek policie jadar lakin e room rent shatra boli nahi hum prefer karbo sehi samasta koyal ...  After
checking your details, you will get it done.
Now post hospitalization means
when your hospital is opened,
when you go to the hospital,
prescription wise medicines are given through doctor's prescription only, home
treatment expenses will be reduced, but
medical insurance covers these general medicines for 30 to
180 days. There are different companies available,
then pre and post hospitalization cost can be covered,
but if you take your insurance, then look at the copay amount, you will have to pay
some percentage, say
10% or 30%, the
rest will be paid by the company, in one
area you will pay 100% of the medical claim, if
your bill is one lakh, you will pay up to
80000, then you can take your
insurance.  Medi claim copay to
apnake tahi karte jakhn apna hospitalization
hove se copay term sle kuchhu taka apnakar
premium kum pade lekin aadat jad zaroor lage jo taka
apna premium bhejne tha ba tak
kharb ho jaye to copay option na avel kar but anad jani rakhla rup je khub important se ho day care treatment dekhna day care treatment cover kina dekhna ka anad bolan cancer chemo therapy deva jana but
hospital
ekta din total rujit hote hoy na day care treatment hoye raakhya bahu important kuchchha karta raakhya
24 ghanta
hospital rujit hova zaroor pade na se jana
apnake medi claim amount kon shaarta de kina
j apnake hospitalle ek ba do din rujit hote hoy tabhi tara
apnake mediclaim jo amount seta payment karbe seta kin khub please
dekhne neve na hole kat khub inconvenience padte paren rup as
policy waiting period
khubh important dekhna bahu rogh rag j waiting
period hoy  There is a waiting period of 30 days for many critical diseases. In case of
multi-
critical diseases there is a waiting period of 9 days for many underlying
diseases. If you have
blood stones then you should get your operation done. If you have blood stones then
your
doctor should tell you to get the operation done in the next two months. If you are facing any
inconvenience then you should get
your treatment done. If you have sugar or high blood pressure then you should get your medical claim done. But if you have sugar or high blood pressure then you should get your medical claim done.
But if you have
sugar or high blood pressure then you should get your medical claim done. But if you have sugar or high blood pressure then you should get your medical claim done. If you have sugar or high blood pressure then you should get your medical claim done. But if you have
sugar or high blood pressure then you should get your medical claim done. If you have sugar or high
blood pressure then you should get your medical claim done. If you have sugar or high blood pressure then you should get your medical claim done.
waiting period terms and conditions
dekhne rakhn apni vipad samay claim paan bole
jhoke pade kon to apna ko rog hone sange
mediclaim lene ta bhey e mediclaim ins the
medical expenses pe jabo seta but nay tra
vigilant tha feature khab import aap hum jana benefit bolo na thakle ani medi claim karab hi na then apni tp the dekhne nen
je company
policy features gulo sega karab first no claim
advantage jd apnakar prap besh kok bare apna kon claim na hoy tale apna no claim bonus hib ki ki advantage paan seta but ani jene nen aage thake nek samay apnakar policy premium amount kame jab nek samay apnakar policy sum es nek company bie de to no claim benefit ki se varsi jene nen nom
benefit j company de bhalo kum no claim
benefit jeta de sehi company but apni g
insurence karab second hoche  Restoration is very
important in health insurance sector,
you can get a maximum amount of money which is Rs.
5 lakhs insurance cover and
medical expenses which can cover up to Rs. 5 lakhs.
Companies can
restore up to Rs. 5 lakhs once
hospitalized, and if you incur Rs. 5 lakhs in
subsequent hospitalizations, you can get the
restoration benefit. There are
three or four conditions for getting your medical insurance coverage. Many
companies provide restoration features if you are admitted twice in a single disease, or if you are admitted three or
three times in a single disease, you can get the
restoration benefit. However, some companies provide
unlimited restoration, some companies provide
restoration benefits twice, but some companies provide ki
tawaali and restoration benefits to their patients.  The fourth point is very important cashless benefit dikna apni jakhn hospital bhiyan disease grivat hole apnakar hate sab samay cash thake na ohhi company ta cashless benefit dikna i.e. apni ko taka na deyen insurance company hospital ki sarsari apnakar bill ta pay kar deb apni ko taka na deyen ba alp kuchh kharbe deyen apni sekha bate
cashless benefit dikna second anek taka reimbursement i.e.
cashless ayak
company ki cashless dilo reimbursement dilo
na now anek company reimbursement
features cashless thake  If you are admitted in a
hospital then you can pay
Rs. 1 lakh to your hospital bill. If you are
admitted in a hospital then
you can pay Rs.
1 lakh to your hospital bill. If you are discharged from the hospital then you can pay Rs.
1 lakh to your
hospital bill. If you are discharged from the hospital then you can pay Rs.
1 lakh to
your hospital bill. If you are discharged from the hospital then you can pay Rs. 1 lakh to your hospital bill. If you are discharged from the hospital then you can pay Rs. 1 lakh to your bank account ...  If you are a
doctor then you can take
medical insurance in the next 24 hours and get it in the next 24 hours. If you are a doctor then you can take it ...  If
you are a Mediclaim Insurance Company then you can avail the Mediclaim Insurance premium by paying premium to the eligible eligible company. If you are a
Mediclaim
Insurance Company then you can avail the Mediclaim Insurance premium by paying
premium to the ...  If you are a person with no claim then you can get no claim
benefit and no claim benefit. ...
aman ekti suvidha di jekhane ja ani
hospital bet na pe bit purvayoj
chikitsa guli karna se kharbh guli khunti policy aavta ast sab majdar bahaya hoche
apni j
amount kon company good feature gulo dekhte paban sarkam ani
ok feature gulo dekhte paban ech
frequency bhag jis karchh tara sega aage the answer diy rekhte phale apni sahje kuntek beshi ma
There is an insurance scheme which is being implemented by the
government under various social
benefit schemes like Ayushman Bharat
Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana, Aam Aadmi
Bima Yojna, Central Government Health Care
Scheme or State Government Swasthya Sathi
Scheme. Firstly, there is a
hospital bed quota,
hospitalization process should be strengthened.
Secondly, there is an upper limit of Rs. 5 lakh,
3 lakh, 2 lakh. If you
spend more money from your pocket, then you can
keep medical insurance or health insurance. Personal
recommendation is given by me because I am happy to
keep my disaster preparation, I am not a habitual victim
of disaster, I am planning for my upcoming festivals, I am
planning for festivals during the festival season,
but it is very important to take medical insurance or health insurance.  Talk Jogan
ki bha karba karan bahut saazhe sahaj sakta karte jaaye sadhna but sakta karte jaaye tai apnakar abaar bol haat jor request ko anad aar aar sakta ...